Wrongfully accused. Unjustly imprisoned. Now he's fighting back.
Undisputed II: Last Man Standing is a action, crime,
thriller film directed by Isaac Florentine.
Heavyweight Champ George "Iceman" Chambers is sent to a
Russian jail on trumped-up drug charges.
In order to win his freedom he must fight against the jailhouse
fighting champ Uri Boyka in a battle to the death.
This time he is not fighting for a title, he is fighting for his life!
George Chambers, played by Michael Jai White.
Yuri Boyka, played by Scott Adkins.
Steven Parker, played by Ben Cross.
Crot, played by Eli Danker.
Gaga, played by Mark Ivanir.
Phil, played by Ken Lerner.
Undisputed II: Last Man Standing is a 2006 American direct-to-video martial arts action film directed by
Isaac Florentine and starring Michael Jai White, Scott Adkins, Eli Danker and Ben Cross.
It is the sequel to the boxing movie Undisputed (2002), and the
second installment in the Undisputed franchise.
White portrays ex-boxer George "Iceman" Chambers, a role
originally played by Ving Rhames in the first film.
It was followed by two sequels: Undisputed III: Redemption (2010) and Boyka: Undisputed (2017),
which continues the story of Russian prison fighter Yuri Boyka, played by Adkins.
The tone is emotional and intense.